sportingo.com 2010-12-31

# - Sportingo

**Privacy Policy**

Last updated: 21 October, 2008

This document contains information regarding our privacy policy and practice and is presented to help you feel comfortable using our website. It is provided for your benefit and describes how we collect and use information. Please take a moment to read the following statement in order to affirm you agree with our practices.  
Sportingo reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time without the requirement of any notice to you. The last modification date will be indicated on the top of this Agreement. 

By using the Sportingo Website ("Website") you permit the usage of your Personal Information and User Generated Content (as such terms are defined below) as outlined below in our Privacy Policy and in the [Terms of Use](http://www.sportingo.com/termsofuse.aspx).

 **COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

Sportingo highly respects your privacy and takes careful measures to insure that any personal information collected by us is used solely in accordance with our privacy policy. It is important for us that you understand both what kind of information is collected and how it is used.  
As part of the Website services users may exchange knowledge, provide information, reviews, and opinions on various sports related topics. In order to fulfill the purpose of our Website, we must collect and display a certain amount of personally identifiable information, the extent of which may vary depending on the type of content provided by users. Below please find a description of the types of information collected and displayed by Sportingo. 

**TYPE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED** When registering as a member and as a writer, or when providing comments, input, feedback, etc, you will be prompted to provide certain personal information, depending on the type of content you provide or service you register. Such prompted information may include your first and last name, mailing address, e-mail address, Instant Messenger ID, and certain location information such as city, state, and/or zip code, as well as other pertinent information ("Personal Information"). You are not obligated to provide all information, in which case, however, please be advised that you may be able to enjoy only part of the services our Website has to offer. Kindly note that Personal Information may also include certain information which is not explicitly submitted by you, as we log your browser-type related information, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp, all users who browse our Website will have such information collected from them.   
As opposed to Personal Information which you may be prompted to provide when using the Website, which primarily is intended for voluntary sharing and transferring of information, you will also be free to provide any kind of non-abusive information of your choice, such as questions regarding various sports topics, answers to other people' questions, self-written articles, your profile photo, images of your choice, video reviews, ratings, and any other kind of content you voluntarily choose to provide ("User Generated Content"). 

**USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Sportingo will not sell, provide, rent, trade, or otherwise share your Personal Information with or to third parties for their promotional use, except as required by subpoena, search warrant or other legal process or in the case where you violate, or Sportingo in its opinion determines that you may violate, the Terms of Use of the Website, or in the event that failure to disclose information will lead to imminent harm to customers or others. Please note, however, that we may use your Personal Information in order to provide you with services our Website offers, as well as provide information to our third party affiliates, solely for the purpose of providing you with services. We may also use your email address to send you updates or news regarding our Website, but you may choose not to receive emails of this type by updating Sportingo at [info@sportingo.com](mailto:info@sportingo.com). In the event that Sportingo undergos a change of control it will be entitled to divulge Personal Information of its users to the new corporation provided that these privacy policies are maintained.

Please be further advised that certain browser-type related information such as, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp data may be used by us to diagnose our service, monitor our servers and make sure we provide you the highest quality of service. In addition, we may use this information to perform statistical analyses of the behavior and characteristics of people using the Website in order to measure interest and use of the various areas of the site. We may also inform advertisers of above mentioned information as well as the number of people who have been exposed to, or clicked on, their advertising banners. Advertisers in turn, may also serve content and/or advertisements and collect information directly from you. 

**USE OF USER GENERATED CONTENT**

Please note that by using this Website you hereby grant Sportingo the licenses set forth in the [Terms of Use](http://www.sportingo.com/termsofuse.aspx) under the "Use of Website Content" section. For further information regarding how your User Generated Content may be used, please refer to our [Terms of Use](http://www.sportingo.com/termsofuse.aspx). 

**CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Due to the nature of the web and the public nature of Sportingo please be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g., sign in name, e-mail address) via posts, messages, forums, etc., such information, along with any substantive information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and used by third parties for various purposes, including unsolicited messages from such third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Sportingo. Please do not include in your User Generated Content any information which you wish to keep private. 

**SECURITY OF INFORMATION** As we are committed to protecting the security of your Personal Information, Sportingo uses various security means and technologies in order to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. 

**COOKIES**  
Upon your first visit to Sportingo, a cookie is sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. A "cookie" is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. Cookies cause no harm to your computer or to your web browsing experience; on the contrary, we use cookies to improve the quality of our service and to better understand how people interact with us.  
Although most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. You can also easily remove any cookie sent to you from our Website. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to use certain services that depend on cookies. 

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISEMENTS**

Please be aware that Sportingo may permit third parties to advertise on the WebSite, in which case advertisements you view shall be run from third party computers. Third parties may send "cookies" to your computer intended for collecting information regarding usage and viewing patterns. Usage of third parties cookies is subject to their privacy policies and not Sportingo' policy. If you wish to learn more about third parties' policies you may do such by visiting their websites. 

**UPDATING AND/OR REMOVING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND PRIVACY PREFERENCES**

Members and writers have the right to access, correct and/or remove their Personal Information and privacy preferences at any time by using the Sportingo Settings page at [please insert a link].   
If you request the removal of your Personal Information, Sportingo will use commercially reasonable efforts to functionally remove you and your Personal Information from the Website. However, please be aware that it may be technically impossible to remove your Personal Information without some residual information being retained by Sportingo. 

**PROTECTION OF CHILDREN'S PERSONAL INFORMATION**

The Website is a general audience website and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 18. 

**LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**  
The Website may contain links to third party websites. Sportingo is not responsible for the privacy practices of these websites (including any cookies sent by third party sites), nor will Sportingo be liable for any content related claim arising from visiting such third party websites. Please be advised that in some cases tracking technology may be installed on your hard drive when you click on a link to a third party website. You may reject the installation of such tracking technology by declining to install/download such technology.

 **PRIVACY-RELATED INQUIRIES AND COMPLAINTS**

If you believe that Sportingo has not complied with this privacy policy with respect to your Personal Information or if you have other related inquiries or concerns, please feel free to contact us at [info@sportingo.com](mailto:info@sportingo.com)

 **GOVERNING LAW**

This privacy policy will be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the laws of England and Wales, without giving effect to its conflict of laws provisions. Any action arising from or related to this privacy policy and the use of our Website will be brought only before the competent courts of England.

 **COPYRIGHT NOTICE**

All rights reserved. © 2008  
SportBuzz Limited
